Guide to the Terence Sellers Papers 1967-2000 MSS.167
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Writing
  - Subseries A: Short Stories, Poetry and Plays
    - "Shit on Heroin: The $200", published in Bomb, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - "Shoe Fetish As Expressed by a Dog", 1982 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - "Stories '86", 1986 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - "Stories '86" continued, 1986-87 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - "A Subjective Analysis of Sexuality in Respect to Prostitution", 1980 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - "The Tarot" for High Times and East West Journal, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - "Tarot of the Moderns", 1979 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - "Teenage Writing Left From the Fire", 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - "Thanksgiving Day With Uncle David" (David McDermott), c. 1978 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - "To Achieve Death", published in Fenris Wolf (Sweden), 1988 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - "To the Best of Women", 1980 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - "Techne-Theory", 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - "The Vampire", undated (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - "Vita Constrictor", 1983 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - "The Voice of Candy", 1993 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - X Magazine, copies of stories, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Amos Poe, Foreigner Script, by Terence, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Writings, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Suicide Letters collection, 1972-1986 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - The Hour of the Fey, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Prose, unevolved, 1972-1986 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - 1973 Diary, 2013 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Marie Stanley letters, typing, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Paranoid, All-seeing Eye, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Marie Stanley, original ms., 1973 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Mistress Angel Stern, undated (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Rules of the Angel, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Reading, Chez Asada, E. Village, New York, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Reading Material, Mother, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Texts for Reading, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - De Sade Readings, 120 Days of Sodom Notes, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Subseries B: Book-length Works
    - The Compleat Masochist: "Parts I and II, original", 1993 (Box 5, Folder 185 A)
    - The Compleat Masochist: Draft of "Editor's Foreward", undated (Box 5, Folder 185 B)
    - The Compleat Masochist: Draft of "The Correct Masochist", undated (Box 5, Folder 185 C)
    - The Compleat Masochist: Draft, undated (Box 5, Folder 185 D)
    - The Compleat Masochist: "Parts I and II, rough draft for re-write", 1993 (Box 5, Folder 185 E)
    - The Compleat Masochist: original wrapper containing folders 185A through E, undated (Box 5, Folder 185 F)
    - The Complete Masochist:Psychoanalytic Diary, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Semitexte: Polysexuality, Coprophagi and Urinology", undated (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Fragments, S&M Theme", undated (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - The Correct Sadist: Journal, December through February, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Early Angel Stern", various (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Angel Stern and Related Scraps", 1977 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Memoirs of Angel Stern", 1978 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - The Correct Sadist: "S&M Dialogues", undated (Box 5, Folder 192 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: "S&M, Raw Materials", various (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - The Correct Sadist: "S&M Raw Material, Not Used", various (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Diary of Maitresse", undated (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Dominance Tricks Manuscripts", 1978 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - The Correct Sadist: "The Cannibal Mouth", undated (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - The Correct Sadist: Various Printed Materials, undated (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - The Correct Sadist: Notes, William James and St. Augustine, undated (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - The Correct Sadist: Notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part One, Originals, Roughs and Corrected Copies, undated (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part I, Original, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part II, Roughs, and Originals, undated (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part II, Originals and Rough Drafts, undated (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part III, unused writings, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part III, "The Beginning", undated (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part III, "Fatal", undated (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part III "The Threshold", 1979 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part III, final rough draft, undated (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 1-22, undated (Box 6, Folder 210)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 23-52, undated (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 53-79, undated (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 53-79, undated (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 80-109, undated (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 140-164, undated (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 165-189, undated (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - The Correct Sadist: copy, pages 1-20, undated (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - The Correct Sadist: copy, pages 21-45, undated (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - The Correct Sadist: copy, pages 46-75, undated (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - The Coreect Sadist: copy, pages 76-106, undated (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - The Correct Sadist: second copy, pages 1-46, undated (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - The Correct Sadist: Author's Forward, undated (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - The Correct Sadist: Index, undated (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - The Correct Sadist: revised manuscript, pages 1-30, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - The Correct Sadist: revised manuscript, pages 31-70, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - The Correct Sadist: revised manuscript, pages 71-106, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - The Correct Sadist: revised manuscript, pages 3-39, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - The Correct Sadist: revised manuscript, pages 1-40, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - The Correct Sadist: French Translation, "Dot Printing", undated (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - The Correct Sadist: French Translation, "Laser Printing", undated (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - The Correct Sadist: Appendix for U.K. publication, undated (Box 6, Folder 231)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part I, Temple Press edition, undated (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part II, U.K. edition, undated (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - The Correct Sadist: Temple Press Proof, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - The Correct Sadist: Note on removed materials, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - The Correct Sadist: Notes on uncorrected silvers pages 1-65, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - The Correct Sadist: uncorrected silvers, pages 66-111, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - The Correct Sadist: 'the last corrections' sent to Lanes, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - The Correct Sadist: First Silver pages 1-163, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - The Correct Sadist: Second Silver print, pages 1-163, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - The Correct Sadist: The Third Silver, pages 11-159, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - The Correct Sadist: printed from PDF, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - The Correct Sadist: Mock-up, pages to scale, undated (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - The Correct Sadist: Duplicate negatives of illustrations by Jeffrey Bretschneider, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 243 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: NY, Vitriol Publications, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 243 B)
    - The Correct Sadist: Specifications for Printers, undated (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - The Correct Sadist: Production Costs, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - The Correct Sadist: Postcards, undated (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - The Correct Sadist: Promotional Materials, undated (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - The Correct Sadist: Promotional Materials, undated (Box 6, Folder 247 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: Promotional Postcards, undated (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - The Correct Sadist: Ads and Press Materials, 1983-1996 (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - The Correct Sadist: Grove Street Press, 1983-1990 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - The Correct Sadist: Grove Press Publication Party, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - The Correct Sadist: Librarie Ernest Flammarion, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - The Correct Sadist: Blue Moon Contract, undated (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - The Correct Sadist: Robert Merodack Contract (French publisher), 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - The Correct Sadist: Italian Publishers, SHAKE, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - The Correct Sadist: Temple Books Contract (U.K. publisher), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - The Correct Sadist: Press Notebook, undated (Box 6, Folder 257)
    - The Correct Sadist: cover letters sent to publishers with manuscripts, c.1981 (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - The Correct Sadist: reviews, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - The Correct Sadist:Lane Publications, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - The Correct Sadist: Poster for reading, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - The Correct Sadist:Times Square Show, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 261 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: Paris Readings, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 261 C)
    - The Correct Sadist:Reading at TR3, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 261 D)
    - The Correct Sadist:Postcard for Reading, undated (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - The Correct Sadist: Blue Moon signing party invitation, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 262 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: Click and Drag Invitations, c.1995 (Box 6, Folder 262 B)
    - The Correct Sadist: Interview in The Face, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - The Correct Sadist: Review in Screw Magazine, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - The Correct Sadist: Review in East Village Eye, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - The Correct Sadist: Reading, The Kitchen, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - The Correct Sadist: Ratso Sloman Interview with Angel Stern, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - The Correct Sadist: Soldes, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - The Correct Sadist: Textuerre, Pose, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - The Correct Sadist: Interview in High Times, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - The Correct Sadist: Harpers Excerpt (with unpublished editing), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - The Correct Sadist: L'Ennemi, Fag Rag, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Part I, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Part II, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Part II continued, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Part II continued, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Part III, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Dungeon Evidence, Velvet Publications, London, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - The Correct Sadist: Dungeon Evidence, Manilla Envelope, undated (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: Diary, January through October, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: Journal February through July, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: Journal, September through December, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: Correspondence with George Coe aka Christopher Coe, author, 1972-73 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: background text, "The Dance", 1973 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: background text, "The Theory of Death", 1973 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: various printed materials, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: poems and short stories, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: background text, poems, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: scripts, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: background text, "Solitude", 1973 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: background text, "Zasu, Gelsomina", 1973 (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: early draft, undated (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: early draft, undated (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: early draft, undated (Box 7, Folder 294)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: first draft, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: first draft, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 1-25, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 297)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 26-50, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 51-75, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 76-102, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 1-25, 1973/2004 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 26-50, 1973/2004 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 51-75, 1973/2004 (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 76-98, 1973/2004 (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: manilla envelope, c.2004 (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - The Degenerate: research notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - The Degenerate: "The Birth of the Psyche", undated (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - The Degenerate: printed materials, "Clinical Descriptions: Psychopath", various (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - The Degenerate: notes from Crime and Punishment, undated (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - The Degenerate: printed materials, excerpts from "Dementia Praecox", 1971 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - The Degenerate: notes from "Sadism and Masochism" by Stekel, undated (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - The Degenerate: notes from "Sadism and Masochism" by Stekel, continued, undated (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - The Degenerate: various printed materials, "Schizophrenics-Speech", undated (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - The Degenerate: new work, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - The Degenerate: notes for "The Solitary", 1980 (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - The Degenerate: notes for "The Solitary", 1980 (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - The Degenerate: early draft, "The Solitary", 1979 (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - The Degenerate: "Aurora", unfinished story, undated (Box 7, Folder 318)
    - The Degenerate: thematics, undated (Box 7, Folder 319)
    - The Degenerate: "Cheri", undated (Box 7, Folder 320)
    - The Degenerate: influences/Rainer/bibliography, undated (Box 7, Folder 321)
    - The Degenerate: "Story of Rainer", 1979 (Box 7, Folder 322)
    - The Degenerate: Journal, Rainer, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 323)
    - The Degenerate: notes, drafts and various printed materials, undated (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - The Degenerate: "Logic of the Elect", appendix, undated (Box 7, Folder 325)
    - The Degenerate: rough drafts, undated (Box 7, Folder 326)
    - The Degenerate: rough drafts, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 327)
    - The Degenerate: Part II, "Insanity", undated (Box 7, Folder 328)
    - The Degenerate: Part II, "Philosophical", undated (Box 8, Folder 329)
    - The Degenerate: Part III, "Corrections", 1987 (Box 8, Folder 330)
    - The Degenerate: Part II, "Robert in the Underworld", undated (Box 8, Folder 331)
    - The Degenerate: "Robert in the Underworld" continued, undated (Box 8, Folder 332)
    - The Degenerate: drafts and revisions, undated (Box 8, Folder 333)
    - The Degenerate: drafts and revisions continued, undated (Box 8, Folder 334)
    - The Degenerate:drats and notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 335)
    - The Degenerate:Anne/Anne and Robert dialogs, her burgeoning masochism, undated (Box 8, Folder 336)
    - The Degenerate: sections, undated (Box 8, Folder 337)
    - The Degenerate: Robert's Diary, pg 120-449, undated (Box 8, Folder 338)
    - The Degenerate: Robert's Diary, pg 453-480, undated (Box 8, Folder 339)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 1-19, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 20-41, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 341)
    - The Degenerate:Part I, pages 42-63, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 342)
    - The Degenerate:Part I, pages 64-87, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 343)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 88-105, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 344)
    - The Degenerate:Part 1, pages 106-130, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 345)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 131-152, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 346)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 152-175b, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 347)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 176-200, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 348)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 201-216, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 349)
    - The Degenerate: submission to agents and publishers, undated (Box 8, Folder 350)
    - The Degenerate: Reading at Montreal, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 351)
    - The Degenerate: Published excerpts, Bomb and Vacation, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 352)
    - The Obsession: Draft, undated (Box 8, Folder 352 A)
    - The Obsession: "Original and one copy", 1976 (Box 8, Folder 352 B)
    - The Obsession: I - draft, undated (Box 8, Folder 352 C)
    - The Obsession: "Original, finished", 1977 (Box 8, Folder 352 D)
    - The Obsession: Final, correct copy pp.1-48, undated (Box 8, Folder 352 E)
    - The Obsession: Final, correct copy pp.49-98, undated (Box 8, Folder 352 F)
    - The Obsession: Final, correct copy pp.99-114, 3-35, undated (Box 8, Folder 352 G)
    - The Obsession: Final, correct copy pp.41-78, undated (Box 8, Folder 352 H)
    - The Obsession: Final, correct copy pp.79-117, undated (Box 8, Folder 352 I)
    - The Obsession: II - original, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 352 J)
    - The Obsession: II - 2nd draft, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 352 K)
    - The Obsession: II - 2nd draft/Corrected, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 352 L)
    - The Obsession: II - original: final, 1979-80 (Box 8, Folder 352 M)
    - The Obsession: III - draft, undated (Box 8, Folder 352 N)
    - The Obsession: Galleys, pieces of, undated (Box 8, Folder 352 O)
    - The Obsession: Galleys, page 33-50, undated (Box 8, Folder 353)
    - The Obsession: Galleys, page 51-65, undated (Box 8, Folder 354)
    - The Obsession: Galleys page 66-80, undated (Box 8, Folder 355)
    - The Obsession: Galleys, page 80-91, undated (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - The Obsession: Boards, undated (Box 8, Folder 356 A)
    - The Obsession: Boards, page 13-39, undated (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - The Obsession: Boards, page 39-59, undated (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - The Obsession: Boards, page 60-78, undated (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - The Obsession: Boards, page 78-92, undated (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - The Obsession: boards, page 93-109, undated (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - The Obsession: Boards, page 111-117, undated (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - The Obsession, softback edition, published by Vitriol Publications, etchings by Carl Apfelschnitt, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 362 A)
    - The Obsession: Promotional materials, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 362 B)
    - The Obsession: "Promotion Mailing", undated (Box 8, Folder 362 C)
    - The Obsession: "Book Binding - Silk/Leather", undated (Box 8, Folder 362 D)
    - The Obsession: "End papers", undated (Box 8, Folder 362 E)
    - The Obsession: "Type styles, misdemeanors", undated (Box 8, Folder 362 F)
    - The Obsession: Production estimates, undated (Box 8, Folder 362 G)
    - The Obsession: Book production costs, undated (Box 15, Folder 362 H)
    - The Obsession: "Money", undated (Box 15, Folder 362 I)
    - The Obsession: Production schedule, undated (Box 15, Folder 362 J)
    - The Obsession: original envelope with annotations, undated (Box 15, Folder 363)
    - The Obsession, 1977-1989 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
    - One Decadent Life: workbook, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 364)
    - One Decadent Life: Draft, Part III, undated (Box 15, Folder 365)
    - One Decadent Life: diskette containing last chapters, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 366)
    - One Decadent Life: A Novel of Manhattan in 1985, pages 1-23, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 367)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 24-47, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 368)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 48-69, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 369)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 70-95, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 370)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 96-115, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 371)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 116-131, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 372)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 132-160, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 373)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 161-183, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 374)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 184-205, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 375)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 206-223, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 376)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 223-239, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 377)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 240-262, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 378)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 263-282, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 379)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 283-303, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 380)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 304-330, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 381)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 331-352, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 382)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 353-378, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 383)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 379-401, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 384)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 402-419, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 385)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 420-441, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 386)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 442-469, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 387)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 470-497, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 388)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 448-525, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 389)
    - One Decadent Life, "Journal of Transition", 1974 (Box 15, Folder 390)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 526-545, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 391)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 546-577, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 392)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Dungeon Evidence, 1991-1997 (Box 51, Box 52)
  - Subseries C: Artwork for Terence Sellers' books
    - The Correct Sadist: pastel drawings by Jeffrey Bretschneider, undated (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - Mistress Manslaughter: watercolor by Terence Sellers, undated (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - The Obsession: Carl Apfelschnitt's charcoal drawings published in 1986 edition, [1985] (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - The Obsession: etchings by Carl Apfelschnitt, [1985-1986] (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - The Obsession: Five duplicate etchings by Carl Apfelschnitt, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 397)
  - Subseries D: Scrapbooks
    - Scrapbook compiled by Terence Sellers containing various printed materials relating to her publications. (Box 10, Folder 398)
  - Subseries E: Publications
    - Dirty, No.6, January-February 1981 (Box 15, Folder 402)
    - Dirty, No.8/9, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 403)
    - Fantacy Register, Issue #2, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 406)
    - Heavy Metal, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 408)
    - High Times, No.42, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 409)
    - Masquerade Magazine, Vol. 7, No.1, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 411)
    - Skin Two, No.10, undated (Box 15, Folder 415)
    - X Magazine, Vol. 1, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 419)
- Series V: Photographic Materials
  This series contains photographs, negatives and slides taken of Terence Sellers and Angel Stern. They are arranged alphabetically by photographer.
  - Prints and negatives of photographs taken by Steve Anderson of Terence Sellers., 1973 (Binder 1, Folder 422)
  - Contact sheets of photographs taken by Amy Arbus of Terence Sellers., 1981 (Binder 1, Folder 423)
  - Photographic prints, negatives, and contact sheets taken by Christopher Coe., c.1972 (Binder 1, Folder 424)
  - Prints and negatives from the "Dungeon Photos" series by Jimmy De Sana of Terence Sellers and unknown model. Binder also includes 2 CD's containing digital image files of the full photo series., 1978-1979 (Binder 1, Folder 425)
  - Prints, negatives, and contact sheets taken by George Du Bose of Terence Sellers, 1982 (Binder 2, Folder 426)
  - Photographic prints by Doris Kloster of Terence Sellers., undated (Binder 2, Folder 427)
  - Photographs by Tony Mendoza of Terence Sellers and Lucian., [1980] (Binder 2, Folder 428)
  - Photographic prints, negatives, and contact sheets by Bobby Miller of Terence Sellers and Angel Stern., various (Binder 2, Folder 429)
  - Photographic prints by Anya Philips of Terence Sellers., 1970s (Binder 2, Folder 430)
  - Contact sheets of "Dr. Stern" taken by Michael Renciwisz, [1990] (Binder 3, Folder 431)